There are six stages or modes of a design sprint.
设计冲刺分为六个阶段或模式
And each of these stages solves an important part of the design process.
每个阶段需要解决设计过程中的一个重要部分
The first phase is the understand phase.
第一个阶段是理解
In this phase, you're trying to get clarity on the business goals,
在这个阶段中 你将试着弄清楚业务目标
the problem you're solving for, technical feasibility, the market, and
你要解决的问题 技术可行性 市场
user needs.
以及用户需求
You've actually already been working on some of this throughout the first two
在课程的前两课中
lessons of the course.
你实际已经学习了这部分内容
And there are other activities that you can do, which I'll cover later.
你还可以进行其他的一些活动 我之后会提到
The second stage is the define stage.
第二个阶段是定义阶段
In this stage, you might define the goal for the product or certain features.
在此阶段中 你要定义产品的目标或特定功能
This might include the positioning, a user journey, or
可能包括定位、用户体验旅程
metrics related to the product or those certain features.
或者与产品或某些特定功能相关的指标
We'll cover more about metrics in lesson 4.
我们会在第四课中进一步讨论指标的问题
Now, this stage is similar to what Richard Fulcher was talking about when
这个阶段与 Richard Fulcher 之前提到的
he mentioned tasks that are related to a user's goals.
确定与用户目标相关的任务是相似的
For example, a user may search for a particular grocery item
比如说 用户可能使用我们的购物应用搜索特定的物品
in our shopping app, which would be then added to the cart for purchase.
然后加入购物车准备购买
The third stage is the diverge stage.
第三个阶段是发散阶段
In this stage, you want to create as many solutions as you can
在这个阶段 你要为初始设计挑战
to the original design challenge.
创造尽量多的解决方案
And this is the stage where you really get to unleash your creativity.
这个阶段中 你需要真正地发挥你的创造性
It's the fun part.
是很有意思的一个环节
The fourth stage is the decide stage, and in this stage,
第四个阶段是决定阶段
you really just want to deliberate about the ideas that you came up with
在这个阶段 你需要认真权衡你在发散阶段
in the previous diverge stage, refine those, and then choose the best one or
想到的创意 进行改进 然后选择最好的一个
some combination of the ideas so that way you get a best possible product.
或者多个创意的组合 以期得到最好的产品
The fifth stage is the prototyping stage.
第五个阶段是原型设计阶段
In this stage, you want to actually create and build the wireframes,
在此阶段中 你需要真正地创建用于用户测试的
the mockups, or the prototypes that you'll actually test with real users.
线框图、模型或原型
These are the deliverables of the design sprint.
这些是设计冲刺的产物
And finally, the last stage is the validation stage.
最后的一个阶段是确认阶段
In this stage, you really want to test your products with real users.
在这个阶段中 你想要与真正的用户测试你的产品
You're testing your wireframes, your mockups, or your prototypes, to
你可以测试你的线框图、模型或原型
determine whether or not the hypotheses, or your risky assumptions are true.
以确定你的假设或最具风险性的设想是否是真的
You're trying to figure out whether or not you have the right product, and
你要试着确认你是否生产了正确的产品
whether or not it's usable.
产品是否可用
So there you have it, the six stages of a design sprint.
所以 你知道了 这就是设计冲刺的六个阶段
Understand, define, diverge, decide, prototype, and validate.
理解、定义、发散、决定、原型、确认
Throughout this lesson, Amir will interview a design sprint master
在本课中 Amir 将和 Google 的一位设计冲刺总管面谈
at Google and talk more about each of these stages.
更多地讨论这些阶段的相关问题
I'll follow those videos by describing activities that you can do
在这些视频之后 我会进一步说明
with each of these stages.
你在每个阶段可以做什么事情
As you watch the videos, think about which activities might be helpful for
在观看视频的过程中 你想一想哪些活动
your specific design challenge.
对你自己的设计挑战有帮助